Surprisingly, I felt like I was doing the same thing as usual,
But I thought that each word of the song would be my last, and I wanted to sing it with care,
As I sang, I thought, "I wish I could have sung more Batten songs.
Sakura is graduating after the release of Q-DEN this time,
I don't think we will have that much time to sing with the current members,
I don't think we can sing with the full 6 members for only about a month after the release of Q-DEN until Sakura's graduation, but I was a little sad to think that it was the last time I could sing with her,
It's a little sad to think that it's the last time she sings, and I'm sure everyone will feel sad too,
I think it will be a little sad to think that this is the last time I will sing, and I am sure you will feel sad too.
I think it's great that the lyrics are about the past and the future, which I have been thinking about for a long time,
The lyrics, which express the feeling of connecting, of course enjoying the present, but also of continuing on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on....
The album is packed with songs we have released so far, and with the addition of two new songs, I think it is an album packed with a lot of songs,
As you can see in the lyrics of the songs, the history of the album is very important, but we will continue to make it even more from now on.
I think Lira will continue to do her best with this 9-year album.
I think "My Kagura" will be one of the most popular songs at our live concerts in the future,
I can imagine ourselves enjoying it live in the future while singing it, and I hope that people will listen to it a lot and that we can make it even better live.
I hope you will listen to it a lot, and I hope we can make it even better in live performances.
I really like this song. The lyrics also include the words "Pan-pan, pan-pan with hands clasped together," "Aiaiaiya," "Waiwaiiya," and other lyrics that naturally brighten people's day and bring smiles to their faces,
I also think that this song is completed with the calls of the members, so I would like to add the "ai-no-te" part,
I'm excited to see how the song will be performed live.
Since it is the first part of the song, I wanted it to have a groove, and there are a lot of people praying,
Can I have a quick listen to the song, which is a bit emotional, as if you are going to weave the thoughts of these people?
Can I listen to it for a moment?
Can I have a listen?
It's so much better now.
Thank you very much.
Can we go for another try?
Yes, sir.
I don't know.
Excuse me, sir.
Can I just take a moment, in the middle, to show you the bird I just saw?
Of course. Of course.
Like the formation.
When new members join the group, Miyu-chan will be the senior member, not the youngest,
Sakura-chan, one of the pillars of singing, will be gone.
In the midst of that, I think that Miyu-chan has her own charm.
She is going to lead with her singing, as if she is saying, "I'm going.
I thought it would be good to make a statement like this.
I thought it would be good to
I was so surprised.
The beginning of a song is very important, isn't it?
I think it determines the mood of the song.
Since I was entrusted with the job, I wanted to make sure the dance was a good one.
I wanted to make sure that the dance was good, so we reshot the song many times,
I was able to make something I was satisfied with,
I would like to do my best to make the song even better in live performances,
I hope you will listen to the song as much as possible.
Thank you very much for listening.
I really think that song is one of the best songs I've ever written.
I thought it was one of the best songs I've ever written, and it was the first thing that set the tone.
The first thing I had to do was to decide on the tension, which was also the most difficult part.
This time, it's called "Kagura," which means "mama kagura" in Japanese.
As the title suggests, "Kagura" means "mama kagura," which is a kind of "mama's cagra," a kind of "cagra" that people used to call health or hunger.
It's a kind of dance that expresses the idea that when people were starving, they would ask the heavens to bless them with good health.
It's a culture where people used to express their hunger through dance, not by asking for blessings from the heavens, but by expressing it.
I think it would be great if the Batten Girls' Troupe could sing and pass it on to the people around them.
I hope that the Batten Girls' Troupe will be able to pass on their songs to the people around them and pass them on.
I hope to pass on the power of the Batten Shoujo-tai to the people who listen to it.
I think that by creating more and more songs, it will not be packaged with the songs, but by performing the songs live again, the songs will be passed on from generation to generation.
I think the songs will be passed on from one generation to the next.
The first one is
Maybe Batten Girl or Canvas of Dreams.
I remember we were recording with a lot of clicking and clacking!
It wasn't the first time I went into the recording room.
but at the time I was like, "What am I going to do?
I didn't really know how to stand up like this.
There were a lot of difficulties at that time.
But recording is something I've always had a problem with.
I've never had a time when I didn't like it, and I look forward to every recording.
I'm very happy to be able to sing the songs of Batten Girls Band as seen from various people's point of view.
That's why we had a lot of fun recording this time and in the past.
I was about to cry when I said, "Please listen to me..." I'm sorry, I just stood up.
I didn't mean to cry at all.
but as I was listening to the song, Sakura took all the notes, and I cut them together behind her...
I felt like I was going to cry if I wasn't careful, but now I'm crying
I don't know... it's not like I'm sad or anything...
I'm just...
I felt like it was really the last one... but...
The director always assigns the lyrics to each song according to their personalities.
But the director always writes lyrics for each song according to each person's personality.
And, um...
I thought the lyrics to "May the laughter continue" were so perfect that I almost cried.
I almost cried.
I wasn't crying... but... after it was announced and we heard it from Sakura... we thought...
I wonder...
I know we're graduating.
But...
Sakura's still here.
I don't know...
I don't know if I really feel it or not.
I think I do, but...
but I don't feel it.
I don't feel like I'm really feeling it.
I'm getting more and more excited about this last part of my life.
From now on
I'm sure I'll realize it each time.
I'm sure I'm going to feel it every time I see it.
It was one of them.
LOL.
Oh my God!
I don't really feel it yet, but...
When I think about it...
I mean...
The words are coming out, but the words aren't coming out.
No, it's not.
The words are coming out, but...
I'm not getting scared,
I'm just... I'm so... eheh!
At first Lili was so nervous about singing,
I was so nervous about recording,
I don't mean to say that I didn't like it,
But I was scared,
I didn't even know if my sound was right or not,
Sakura-chan was always so kind to me and taught me so much about sound and singing,
She was like a great support for me,
Sakura-chan, you're kind of like a friend to everyone,
There were times when I was afraid to sing in front of so many people,
But when I was close to Sakura-chan, I could vocalize my voice and sing,
It was easier to sing with Sakura-chan.
I felt a sense of security with Sakura-chan, and she had always been a big part of Lilah's life, so I feel a little sad... a little sad, but very sad.
I want to support and cheer for you a lot in the future, and I wish you happiness in the future, so please eat a lot of delicious meals and have a lot of delicious meals.
I wish you lots of delicious meals, lots of delicious meals, and lots of fun!
Let's live happily!
Hey, please stop it!
Oh, Tenson Carlin. Oh, Tenson Carlin.
Oh, yeah. I did this once, earlier. Do you have a friend named Kaori-chan?
Kaori-chan.
Kaori-chan? A friend.
I had a friend in junior high school.
Wasn't she called Kaorin?
Kaorin.
They didn't call you Kaolin? It was a nickname.
Yes, I was.
No, I'm not.
Kaolin.
That's the same, Kaolin.
It's like Tengsongkha-rin.
Tengsongkha-ling.
Ah, yes. That might work.
So I want you to say Korin like a nickname, like Kao Ling.
Yes.
Carlin.
Yeah. That's good, that's good.
Yes, that's good.
Hey, wait a minute.
Please.
You don't sound like Colin at all anymore. Listen one more time.
Yes.
Whenever I write a song, I always think it's good, but I'm always worried about how people will sing it or what they will think of it,
When I listen to the demo tape, I put my own voice into it, not theirs, so I am a little unsure of the image,
But as I listen to the demo tape with my own voice in it, not theirs, I can't quite grasp the image, but as the voices of the girls start to come in, I feel a sense of relief, and the song really improves with the help of their voices. Thank you very much.
Yes, it is. I thought it was quite magnificent.
Takachiho is big, isn't it? I sang with the scenery of Takachiho in Miyazaki in my mind,
I sang songs like "Battenson descends" and "God is watching over us from the top of Takachiho," and I felt as if God was protecting me,
I felt like God was there, protecting me,
I felt like God was protecting me, like he was there,
I felt like I was there.
Shinobu-san often writes songs for me at each turning point of my career,
Every time, I had a vague feeling,
I was thinking about something that I couldn't even put into words,
I was thinking about something that I couldn't even put into words, or something that I had been thinking about,
I always get it, and I'm always happy to hear it,
I always get something from him,
It is a strange experience for me to see and hear them and realize my feelings again.
Strange? I don't know. It's amazing.
You've already made it into a thing, haven't you?
Okay, then, Ras 1.
Yes, sir.
Final Luster, please.
Please.
I'm going to start the story of the unknown.
The lyrics "Not in vain, it's the history of my life" are amazing.
It's pretty early in the song, but I thought it was very moving.
I'm graduating this time, and I'm a little anxious about going on a different path from being an idol,
I felt that there was this unknown story to be told. I was also worried about what would happen to me in the future,
I was also very excited when I heard about the unknown story, and it really cheered me up to do my best,
I have been active as an idol for about 10 years, and I am really happy to sing this song,
I've been an idol for about 10 years, but I'm really happy to sing this song, it brings back memories of my past, and I really like the lyrics.
Music
Yes, I have the battening down the hatches. But I want it to go beyond the sea, or rather, I want it to go beyond the sea,
There are no idol groups that can convey the traditions of Kyushu,
I wish more and more people would listen to their music.
That's right.
I want more and more people to listen to them.
It's like a hip-hop crew!
Hip-hop, yes.
Completely.
I think it's super cool.
Nowadays, a lot of things can be recorded digitally.
but it's like a culture that could only be passed on through people.
I've been writing songs based on the culture that was only transmitted through people.
I wanted to establish one of those things with this.
Songs like "Antagatadokosa" and "Denderaluva" are playful songs that I don't even know who wrote them.
or songs that we don't even know who wrote them....
The kind of romance that people used to have in the past
And there are remnants of the romanticism of the past that remain in the places where they were written.
I feel it is very rewarding to be able to make music of such things.
And I feel that everyone is getting along well with it.
I think the fans have different opinions.
It's all about me.
I've been watching for many more years.
I feel that way.
I only see them once in a while.
I'm like, "What are you talking about?
Maybe...
It's my own way of thinking about everyone.
So I can't help it.
That's how I feel.
Nice to meet you.
Let's make it last!
The Batten Girls' Corps is going through a period of change.
The batten girls' group is going through a change.
It's filled with determination for the future.
But I guess it's like this.
It's not just about singing about how they're going to do their best from now on.
but also thinking back to the past
This is how we have been up to now, right?
Yes, we have.
We're going to take that into consideration and move forward even more from now on.
It's a feeling that we are not finished here yet.
New members joined the group
I think it fits the concept of the palace that this song will be sung over and over again.
Of course, it's the voices of the 6 members that will remain on the recording, but after Sakura's graduation, I think it's going to be a little bit different.
But after Sakura's graduation, I think we'll be able to show a new style of music from the palace.
I hope this song will be passed on to the next generation even if the members change.
Thank you for listening!